jemsite.com 2014-02-19

# Jemsite - FAQ: Privacy Statement

### Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. We will never contact you, unless you request us to. We will never transfer or sell your personal information to anyone except in the limited extraordinary circumstances described below.

This Privacy Policy describes how we collect and use information and our efforts to protect your privacy. It applies to all of the personal information collected and received in connection with the Website (http://www.jemsite.com).

### Collecting of Information

We log information, such as your ip address and the following of the links in the Website.  
We collect personal information when you sign in for certain features of the service. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable (such as name, physical or email address and phone number) and is not otherwise publicly available.  
We may store and process information collected on the Website in its facilities worldwide.

### Use and Sharing of Information

**We never make your e-mail address available to any other person, unless we have your consent or under the circumstances described below:**

  * We conclude that we are required to disclose such information by law or a governmental agency or in connection with actual or threatened lawsuits, and we believe that the disclosure is appropriate.
  * In connection with our use of third parties' tools and services solely for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. 
  * We have a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is necessary to protect our rights, property, safety or the public.
  * The information shared is anonymous and does not contain any personally identifying information, such as statistics about our users, traffic patterns and information related to the Website or the service.

With the exception of your email and password, any information you give us might appear on our website.  
We use information we collect to operate, develop and improve our Website and services, to conduct research, to handle complaints and disputes, to gather statistics and to provide anonymous reports for internal and external use.  
We or our assets may be acquired and in such case, we cannot guarantee that this Privacy Policy will remain in effect.

### Security

We implement security measures with the goal of protecting your personal information against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction. 

### Cookies

In order to improve the quality of our service, upon visiting the Website, we send to your computer cookies (small files containing a string of characters). The cookies uniquely identify your browser and your preferences, and enable storing your preferences with respect to the Website and the service and to recognize recurring visitors. You may block our cookies if your web browser software permits it. 

### Links

We have no control over and are not responsible for the practices or content of the sites linked from the Website or the service. These other sites may place their own cookies on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information.

### Amendments to the Privacy Policy

#### ValueClick

We have contracted with ValueClick to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisement "click-throughs," and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, ValueClick may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile statistics about our website visitors. For more information about how information is collected and used by ValueClick, please see ValueClick's privacy policy.

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time(s) and in our sole discretion, upon posting notice on the Website.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy please [contact us.](http://www.jemsite.com/forums/sendmessage.php)
